[{"answer": "There's girls everywhere.  I go out of my apartment, there's girls in the elevator.  They're in cafeterias, subways, so what", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Stranded.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "Got it", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "There's a hundred different things here. What's the difference between these two?   You got propylparabin", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Stranded.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "You got isobutan", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Got it", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Stranded.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "I got isobutan", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Stranded.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "Got it", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Excuse me, I gave you a twenty dollar bill and you only actually gave me change for a ten", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Stranded.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "I'm positive I gave you a twenty", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "You gave me a ten", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Stranded.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "I know what you gave me", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "You came all the way out from that place for this", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Stranded.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "So what do you do", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "Are you?  Lemme ask you something. Where do you get your material", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Stranded.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "What kind of voice", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "How come you keep tapping your head", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Stranded.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "On the other hand, you take a guy like my friend.  The man devoted his whole life to the peanut.  Imagine having so much passion for something. Cut back to my friend and his 'guy'", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "Anyway, I'm ready to go", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Stranded.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "If not now, when", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "Wow", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Stranded.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "Go!  What could you do", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "What", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Stranded.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "I long for you", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Well, what are we gonna do for a ride", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Stranded.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "You don't know", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "Well, talk to me when you stop eating fish", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Stranded.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "How do you know?  Do you communicate with fish", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "Why", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Stranded.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "What do you mean, you got it", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "You're a lunatic", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Stranded.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "What do you say to a person like you", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "You don't think I remember you", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Stranded.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "I know who you are, I was watching you", "qsentId": 34}]